( WOMAN MOANING )
( BEDSPRINGS SQUEAKING )
( MOANING )
Mm . Oh , yeah , baby .
Oh , yeah .
( PANTS )
I 'm gonna take a shower .
( DOOR CLOSES )
( SHOWER RUNNING )
( WIND CHIMES RATTLING )
( TWIGS SNAPPING )
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( WHIRRING )
( THE DWIGHT TWILLEY BAND 'S " LOOKING FOR THE MAGIC " PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS )
♪ All my life I 'm looking for the magic ♪
♪ I 've been looking for the magic ♪
♪ Fantasize on a sexy little tragic ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
♪ Stay a while till the city is a desert ♪
♪ She 's been looking for the treasure ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
♪ Oh , in her eyes To keep , oh , oh , oh ♪
♪ The magic in her eyes ♪
♪ Baby , in my eyes ♪
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( GASPING )
( SCREAMING )
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
Huh . Looks like Erik Harson 's home .
PAUL : Yeah . I heard he left his wife for some college student .
He might be living here full time now .
Oh , that 's a shame .
We 're so isolated up here , it might be nice to have a neighbor .
I guess .
I got this . Okay .
That 's funny .
What ?
It 's open .
Doesn 't look like anyone 's been in here .
Oh , you know , I bet the workmen left the door open last time they were here .
I 'll get the groceries out of the car and check on the furnace .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
So your parents are pretty loaded , right ?
Yeah , I guess .
My dad retired from KPG last year , and he got an insane severance package .
Wait , KPG ? As in , the defense contractor ?
Yeah .
He was just in marketing , though .
Why ?
Is that a problem for you , babe ?
Having dinner with fascists ?
No . No . I want to meet your family .
I hope this means there 's gonna be some good booze at your place , though .
( SIGHS )
Probably not . My mom 's on medication .
Can we stop somewhere and get some , then ?
Yes , we should . Good call . Heh . Yes .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( THUDDING )
( FOOTSTEPS )
Hey , I lit the furnace . Sorry .
You Okay ?
Were you just upstairs ?
No , I was in the basement .
Did you hear that , just now ?
Hear what ? I heard footsteps .
I think someone 's in the house . Are you sure ?
Paul , we gotta get out of here !
Aubrey . Hurry up !
No . You go outside . I 'm gonna check the upstairs .
You come outside with me ! It 's a creaky old house .
Paul ! There is someone up there !
( SIGHS )
I 'll take this with me . Okay ? Are you happy ?
No !
All right . You wait outside . I 'll be out in a minute .
Careful . I will .
( FLOORBOARD CREAKING )
Hello ?
( FOOTSTEPS )
( THUMPING )
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
Oh !
Crispian ! Dad .
You scared the shit out of me ! Yeah .
( BOTH CHUCKLING )
Oh , God .
Not to get off on the wrong foot here ,
but why is Mom in the driveway crying ?
Oh , God . Come with me .
( DOOR CLOSES )
( FOOTSTEPS DESCENDING STAIRS )
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
Hey .
( AUBREY SOBBING )
You Okay ?
Crispian and I looked in every room on the second floor . There 's nobody there .
AUBREY : Oh , God .
I 'm so silly .
( SNIFFLES )
Honey , I 'm sorry . No . No .
You 're embarrassed . PAUL : No , I 'm not .
You must be Erin . ERIN : Yes .
Nice to meet you . ERIN : Nice to meet you .
Glad you could make it . Yeah , thanks for having me .
Hey , you . Come here .
It 's okay .
Oh , we brought whiskey .
Well , come on in .
We 'll be there in a minute .
Heh . What 's going on ?
I ... I- - Don 't ask . I don 't know .
So your dad bought this place to fix up ?
Yeah . Supposed to be his retirement project ,
something for him to work on , but I 'm pretty sure so far
he 's just paid other people to work on it .
Hey !
( BEDSPRINGS SQUEAK )
You 're gonna break this bed . It 's like a hundred years old .
Sorry . Your folks seem cool .
I mean , for people with money . You 're lucky .
( SCOFFS )
I guess . No , you are .
You don 't know what most people would give to have folks like yours .
( CRISPIAN SIGHS )
Whatever that means .
( CHUCKLES )
Come here .
So your brothers and sister get in tomorrow ?
Yeah . Tomorrow is my parents actual anniversary .
Thirty-five years , can you imagine ?
No . I can 't , really .
( BOTH CHUCKLING )
Well , I look forward to meeting the rest of your family tomorrow .
They 're something .
It 's been a long time since we 've all been together
so it should be interesting .
How so ?
You 'll see .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( CREAKING )
( MAN 1 SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON TV )
( MAN 2 SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY )
MAN 2 : Not in person ? WOMAN : It 's crazy .
ERIN : Not in person . MAN 2 : Like old black and white videos .
ERIN : You 've seen them . You 've seen the videos .
But when they stand up , they 're taller than you , and if they 've got baby ...
I feel like kangaroos fight guys named Gentleman Jack .
It 's serious . Like , twisty , curly .
Hey . How you doing ?
Morning . Good morning .
Good morning . Hey , buddy .
You ever see kangaroos fight ?
Stop ! KELLY : Okay , okay .
Kelly ? Do some funny little ...
Up on their tails ? KELLY : Okay .
Ow ! Don 't hit me .
Stop it . Come on .
Pussy . Don 't .
You almost hit my face .
KELLY : Crispian ...
DRAKE : Don 't kiss him . Don 't kiss my wife . It 's rude .
Ugh . Gross ! That is sick . Thank you .
Come here and kiss me .
KELLY : Oh , I 'm sorry . He 's your brother . DRAKE : Yeah .
KELLY : I 'm not allowed to kiss your brother .
Reminds me of when you were a kid . You should 've seen him .
No , you shouldn 't have . Oh , yeah ?
DRAKE : Yeah . He was like a little chubby angel .
Really ? KELLY : A little cherub .
DRAKE : Yeah . I was always a little chubby .
He says " only a little chubby . " CRISPIAN : I have a round face .
That doesn 't mean I 'm fat . It doesn 't mean he 's fat .
ERIN : It means you 're beautiful . DRAKE : All the fat on him means he 's fat .
Don 't go just by his face . CRISPIAN : I 'm not fat .
( PAPER RUSTLING )
Hey .
Oh , hello .
Um , I was just wondering if you need any help in here with anything .
I think I 'm all set .
Okay . Actually ... Erin ?
Yeah ? I am out of milk .
Oh . Uh , okay .
Could you go over to the neighbor 's house
and see if he has some ? His name 's Erik .
Okay .
Well , I 'll be right back .
PAUL : How 's this look , Drake ?
DRAKE : Beautiful . Great color .
PAUL : Grain looks nice , doesn 't it ? DRAKE : Yeah .
CRISPIAN : I don 't know about this grain .
What 's going on over here ? Work .
Hey , babe .
ERIN : Boys . You look so adorable .
Can you hold that ?
Ready ?
Beautiful . Come join us , Erin .
Your mom just asked me to go to your neighbor 's
to see if I could borrow some milk .
Really ? ERIN : Yeah .
CRISPIAN : All right . I 'll be back in a minute .
PAUL : Sounds like your mom . DRAKE : That 's right .
Don 't start . Don 't start with me .
I 'm gonna go check on Kelly .
Looks so good , Dad . PAUL : Thanks , Drake .
So how 'd that fellowship thing turn out ?
Oh . Uh ...
Not so good .
No ?
No . Uh ...
I guess there were a lot of applicants this year , and ...
I haven 't exactly been published recently , so ...
Well , there are some people that aren 't published
that do get the fellowship , you know .
Shut the door .
Where 'd your brother find that girl ?
I don 't know . Student ? Former student ?
Huh .
Current student .
( SCOFFS )
I 'll bet she 's kind of annoying .
Accent 's just , like , so jarring to me .
( THUDDING )
( FOOTSTEPS )
Hey , I lit the furnace . Sorry .
You Okay ?
Were you just upstairs ?
No , I was in the basement .
Did you hear that , just now ?
Hear what ? I heard footsteps .
I think someone 's in the house . Are you sure ?
Paul , we gotta get out of here !
Aubrey . Hurry up !
No . You go outside . I 'm gonna check the upstairs .
You come outside with me ! It 's a creaky old house .
Paul ! There is someone up there !
( SIGHS )
Babe , don 't .
Okay . I don 't ... I 'm not feeling this right now , okay ?
Don 't give me that look .
( SCOFFS )
( SIGHS )
Do you have any Vicodin ?
Yeah . It 's in my purse .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( THE DWIGHT TWILLEY BAND 'S " LOOKING FOR THE MAGIC " PLAYING FAINTLY OVER SPEAKERS )
♪ Oh , in her eyes To keep , oh , oh , oh ♪
♪ The magic in her eyes ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
( CLEARS THROAT )
( WHIRRING )
( THE DWIGHT TWILLEY BAND 'S " LOOKING FOR THE MAGIC " PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS )
ERIN : Hello ? Is anyone home ?
( KNOCKING ON DOOR )
♪ All my life I 'm looking for the magic ♪
♪ I 've been looking for the magic ♪
♪ Fantasize on a sexy little tragic ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪ ♪
( ENGINE STOPS )
Aimee !
Hi , Mommy !
Oh , honey .
Look at you ! You are so beautiful .
AIMEE : Thank you . I lost a little weight . AUBREY : You look great .
AIMEE : Thank you . AUBREY : You must be Tariq .
Yes . Nice to meet you . AUBREY : Nice to meet you .
My little Felix . Hi , Mom .
I 'd like you to meet Zee , my girlfriend .
AUBREY : Zee ?
With two E 's . Z-E-E .
Wow . That 's unique . Nice to meet you , Zee .
Come on inside , everyone . Come in .
AIMEE : Where 's Crispian ?
Did he bring his new girlfriend ?
( LAUGHS THEN SQUEALS )
This is my boyfriend . TARIQ : Hi .
Crispian . How you doing ?
You must be Erin . ERIN : Yes .
Oh , my gosh . You 're so beautiful . ERIN : Oh-ho-ho .
Thank you ! Hey . Good to see you .
You 're Erin ? Yeah . Nice to meet you .
Nice to meet you . Heard a lot about you . Oh . And , Zee , right ?
Erin . I know .
PAUL : Hey , where 's my princess ? AIMEE : Daddy !
( BOTH LAUGHING )
This is my boyfriend , Tariq .
How are you ? Welcome . Nice to meet you . Thank you .
Who 'd like a glass of wine ?
I would . I 'll take some wine .
Let me take care of that right now . Felix .
Dad .
AUBREY : I just want you all to know
( VOICE BREAKING ) how much it means to us that you 're all here . So ...
Thank you for coming .
Oh . She 's so cute . I 'm in love . Shh .
( UTENSIL CLINKING ON GLASS )
PAUL : Let 's bow our heads .
Dear Heavenly Father ,
we thank thee for thy food .
Feed our souls on the bread of life ,
and help us to do our part , with kind words
and loving deeds . Amen .
ALL : Amen .
And thanks to Mom and Dad .
For having us all here together .
PAUL : It 's our pleasure .
( CHATTERING )
Um , so , Tariq , what do you do ?
Uh , ahem . I 'm a filmmaker .
Is that right ? AIMEE : Yeah . He 's really good .
I don 't think I know any filmmakers . That is so ...
interesting . TARIQ : There 's not a lot of us .
KELLY : Have you been on TV ? Not on TV .
I 've only made one documentary ,
it was at the Cleveland Underground Film Festival , 2008 .
What is an underground film festival ?
Do they show the movies underground ?
TARIQ : No , no . They show them aboveground , but they ...
They show intellectual films .
DRAKE : So like an intellectual film festival ?
Do you do commercials ? Because those are my favorite .
AIMEE : No , he doesn 't do commercials . Mm-mm . No .
Really ? I just think that is just the height of the art form these days .
It is just short and punchy ,
you really gotta just zing the ideas on in there .
That 's why I watch TV . I just think it 's so ...
It 's better than the shows now .
He makes documentaries , so ... It 's different .
Yeah , but I think that I 've seen documentary commercials .
I don 't think they have to be limited to any particular thing .
It 's not a ... You know , I mean ,
the starving-artist thing just never made sense to me .
I just think you should consider it , Tariq . TARIQ : Sure .
ERIN : That 's no fair !
CRISPIAN : Give it back . That was mine .
ERIN : Stealer .
So , Erin , are you still in school ? Um ... Heh .
Yes . I am . I 'm in my final year .
I 'm finishing my Master 's .
That 's great , good for you . KELLY : In what ?
ERIN : In literature .
Wow . So were you a student of Crispian 's ?
I was . But I 'm not anymore .
Not anymore . Mm-mm .
She was my TA ,
but we stopped , because we figured that that was inappropriate .
( SOFTLY ) It 's a little unprofessional .
What ?
( IN NORMAL VOICE ) What 's that ?
CRISPIAN : What you just said . What was that ?
About what ? You said it 's unprofessional .
Is there something else you wanted to say to me ?
DRAKE : No , I was just agreeing with you . You weren 't agreeing with me .
I mean , I- - What he- - ?
I thought he said it was unprofessional ? Don 't look at her . I 'm right here .
Crispian . What ?
PAUL : We 're having a dinner here .
I 'm having a conversation with my brother .
Is there something that you wanna say , because I feel like- -
I don 't know what you want . I don 't think that you 're in any position
to be judging my moral decisions . Who says I 'm judging you ?
CRISPIAN : You are , with your eyes . It 's a big semantics conversation .
CRISPIAN : The whole time you 've been here
you 've been needling me , and I 'm not putting up with it .
DRAKE : You are so jealous of me . I 'm jealous of you ?
Do we have to do this at the dinner table right now ? Please , I ...
( ARGUING INDISTINCTLY )
CRISPIAN : I 'm jealous of you ?
DRAKE : Always been jealous of me . What have I done ?
Who have I been jealous of ? DRAKE : I make more money than you .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( ARGUING CONTINUES )
AUBREY : Every time we have dinner , you have to argue like this ?
Paul , can you get a handle on these boys ?
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
PAUL : Crispian , your mother 's upset .
What the fuck is that ?
DRAKE : Look in the mirror !
CRISPIAN : You look like The Elephant Man .
( ARGUING CONTINUES )
CRISPIAN : What can you not ? What can you not believe ?
Go ahead and tell me what you can possibly not believe .
What could come out of your mouth that 's interesting or of merit or value ?
I mean , I 've had enough .
( TARIQ CHOKING )
( ALL SCREAMING )
Ow ! Aah !
AIMEE : Oh , my God !
( SCREAMING )
Oh , my God ! Aah !
Help me . Crispian !
Help me get her up . We have to get out of here !
Aimee , no !
DRAKE : Mom , get down ! Get away from the window !
( GROANS )
Aah ! PAUL : Drake !
( DRAKE SCREAMING )
CRISPIAN : Is he all right ?
AUBREY : Oh , my God !
( DRAKE SCREAMING )
PAUL : Aubrey , get down !
ERIN : Get down , get down , get down !
PAUL : Stay down , stay down ! ERIN : Get down , get down !
Stay away from the windows . Get down !
Crispian ! Get Drake , get over here .
Drake ! Stay down !
KELLY : Someone fucking do something !
Hey , hey , hey . It 's okay . It 's okay .
Look at me . You 're gonna be fine , okay ? Just stay down . Okay . We gotta call 911 .
We 're all gonna die !
I don 't have a signal . I don 't have one , either .
ERIN : Does anybody have a signal ? I had a signal today .
I was able to use the phone today ! Dad ! Dad , they must be using a jammer .
What ? A cell-phone blocker .
They 're illegal , but you can get them on the Internet for 30 bucks .
Felix , you fucking low-life !
What are you calling me a low-life for ? I 'm just trying to help .
DRAKE : That 's no fucking surprise you 're into that sketchy shit !
( ALL SCREAMING )
Oh , my God ! We 're gonna fucking die ! Oh , my God !
ERIN : Crispian , grab your brother and carry him out of this room !
Go , go , go ! Go , go , go !
Okay . You 're gonna grab this chair .
Get yourself out of here ! Cover your face and run !
Stay low ! Go !
Aimee , go ! Grab the chair ! Go !
( SCREAMING )
Aubrey ? Aubrey ? Aubrey , Aubrey .
No , I can 't ! No !
PAUL : I 'm here with you . It 's gonna be okay . Come on . Let 's go ! Ready ?
ERIN : Go , go , go ! Come on .
( PANTING )
( GRUNTS )
We have to pull this out , right ? DRAKE : Yes .
Somebody pull it out ! Pull it out ! AUBREY : Maybe we should ...
No , no , no , no . No clipping , no pulling .
Can you just gently place your hands over the wound slightly ? That 's it .
( DRAKE SCREAMING )
ERIN : Breathe ! DRAKE : No , no , no , no . Don 't do it .
No . Stop ! KELLY : I 'm sorry .
DRAKE : Drugs , babe ! Find me drugs !
My purse . Someone hand me my purse . DRAKE : Stop moving ! Aw , fuck !
ERIN : Keep your hands on it , please ! DRAKE : No , don 't ! Oh !
Stop !
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
Oh , my God . What is happening to us ?
What the hell is going on ? I have no fucking idea .
FELIX : Dad , do you see anyone ? I don 't . Do you see anyone ?
No . Somebody should make a run
for the cars . And try to go get help !
AUBREY : No ! We can 't go out there .
It 's the only way . It 's the only way we 're out of this .
Whoever 's the fastest runner . Who is that ?
DRAKE : I 'm the fastest , but I 've got this fucking arrow in my back .
CRISPIAN : What does your shoulder have to do with your legs ? I 'm the fastest .
He has a fucking arrow in his back ! Stop yelling at me , Kelly !
How the fuck do you know it has to do with your legs if you never run , you fat fuck ?
I 'm not fat anymore ! Damn it ! Shut the fuck up !
( ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY )
I 'm the fastest ! You guys never give me any credit for anything !
Look , it 's not about that . Nobody needs to run .
We need to ah stay inside . You don 't believe in me !
Honey , we believe in you . We believe in you .
I can run three miles in 23 minutes . I 'm gonna do it .
Aimee , no ! No ! FELIX : Aimee , you can do this .
I believe in you , okay ?
Just get out where you can make a phone call to get help .
Zee , help me move this . Help me get this out of the way .
PAUL : Felix !
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
I can do this , Daddy . Get down !
FELIX : We 'll pull the doors open at the last second .
They 're not gonna be expecting her to be coming out full speed .
( WHIMPERING )
( NECK CRACKING )
( ALL SCREAMING )
( GASPING )
PAUL : Help us ! Help me !
Get her inside ! Help me ! Baby !
What happened ? What happened ?
( SCREAMING )
PAUL : Aimee !
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( AUBREY KELLY SCREAMING AND SOBBING )
( CHOKING )
AUBREY : Oh , my God . My baby !
Oh , God . Oh , God . Oh , no !
Oh , my God !
Oh , no . My God .
( AUBREY KELLY SCREAMING AND SOBBING )
CRISPIAN : Erin !
What are you doing ?
( LOCKS CLICKING )
We need to make sure all the doors and the windows are locked .
What ?
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( SIGHS )
( WINDOW CLOSES )
( LOCK CLICKS )
Babe . Hey . What are you doing ?
Some places , if you text 911 , they get it as a voice-mail .
If you even have one bar you can send a text . Come on !
Those things are useless .
I 'll have to keep trying .
( AUBREY SOBBING )
Okay , the second floor is clear .
Should be safer than down here . PAUL : Aubrey , come on .
Come on . Come on . AUBREY : No .
Oh , my God , no . I 'm taking her upstairs .
ERIN : That 's a good idea .
Drake , we need to take care of this shoulder .
It 's fine . I can 't feel it anymore . Are you sure ?
Don 't touch it . Don 't touch it .
Okay , we 're all gonna get out of this .
We need to cover up and lock all the windows .
I 've never seen you act like this before . Well , it 's a unique situation .
We still need someone to go and try to get some help .
We should stay in and lock everything , and wait till the police come .
In fact , we should hang a sign out an upstairs window , SOS or something .
That 's a good idea . I can pull a sheet off the bed upstairs .
( AUBREY WHIMPERING )
PAUL : We 're almost there . Come on .
Stay with me .
I have to go check on the kids .
( WHIMPERING )
( SNIFFLING )
( DOOR CLOSES )
( SOBBING )
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( AUBREY GASPS )
( AUBREY SCREAMS )
( THUD )
( SCREAMS )
( GROANING )
DRAKE : Get out of the way ! Move !
CRISPIAN : Oh , my God .
Mom .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
Oh , no . No ! No ! No ! Oh , God ! No !
No ! Aubrey ! No !
Oh , no ! No !
( SOBBING )
I have to go see her . I have to go see her !
DRAKE : Dad , Dad . No . Stay down here .
Stay down here with us .
( SOBBING )
Why would anybody do this ?
( FLOORBOARDS CREAKING )
( LOCK CLICKS )
( SCREAMING )
KELLY : Oh , my God !
( SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY )
Kelly ! No , Drake !
Drake ! DRAKE : Kelly !
( SCREAMS )
Fuck !
( GROANING )
What happened ?
( KELLY SCREAMING )
Help ! Somebody help me !
Somebody help ! Help me !
Can you grab a rag ? FELIX : Yeah , okay .
Maybe we should try to run . I mean , Kelly made it .
At least get to a car or something .
I 'll try . I 'll try . You guys stay here .
No , no , no . Wait . I 'll come with you . Zee , hold this .
But we 'd have to carry Drake . And Dad ...
He ... He can 't run right now .
I 'll go get the car . I 'll bring it right up to the front door .
Then you and Felix and Zee carry Drake and Dad out .
Make sense ?
Babe , it 'll be okay .
I can do this .
It 'll be just a second .
Honey ?
Take this .
( SOBBING )
( THE DWIGHT TWILLEY BAND 'S " LOOKING FOR THE MAGIC " PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS )
♪ Oh , in her eyes To keep , oh , oh , oh ♪
♪ The magic in her eyes ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
Hello ? Sir ? Sir ? Let me in !
Let me in ! What the fuck is wrong with you ?
Open the fucking door ! Unlock the door ! Let me in ! Hello ! Hello !
( WHIMPERING )
♪ Stay a while till the city is a desert ♪
( PANTING )
♪ She 's been looking for the treasure ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
♪ Oh , in her eyes To keep , oh , oh , oh ♪
♪ The magic in her eyes ♪
( SOBBING )
♪ Baby , in my eyes Baby , in my eyes ♪
( SHRIEKS )
♪ ls like an hourglass sometime ♪ ♪
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( KELLY COUGHING )
( KELLY SCREAMS )
( PANTING )
( WHIRRING )
( DWIGHT TWILLEY 'S " LOOKING FOR THE MAGIC " PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS )
♪ All my life I 'm looking for the magic ♪
♪ I 've been looking for the magic ♪
♪ Fantasize on a se- - ♪ ♪
I think it 's safe to assume the other cars are out , but ...
( PANTING )
I didn 't see anybody out there .
Maybe Kelly ... Maybe she got past them .
I mean , it gives us a chance . What do you mean ?
I 'm going back out there .
No , you 're not . CRISPIAN : Yeah .
Yeah . I mean , I didn 't see anyone . Maybe it 's over .
Wait , so what , you 're just gonna leave the rest of us here ?
Clearly , we need some help , man .
We need to get somebody out there , in here .
I 'm gonna go to the neighbor 's .
As soon as I 'm a safe distance away , I 'll try to text and call .
You guys stay in here . Keep each other safe .
I 'll come back . I 'll come right back .
ERIN : Wait , Crispian .
Don 't go . I 'm serious .
Everything 's gonna be fine out there .
You just stay in here .
Take care of yourself .
I 'll come back soon , okay ? Okay ?
You promise ?
I promise .
See you soon .
( LOCK CLICKS )
I think it 's safe to say at least one of them is already inside .
You think the person who killed my wife is still in this house ?
I 'd assume so , yeah .
How is he , Zee ?
Looks like the bleeding stopped .
Let 's get him in there , hide him someplace safe .
Felix , can you give us a hand ?
On three . One , two , three .
( GRUNTING )
What 's the best room for us all to be in ?
All the rooms have windows in them , except for the basement .
No , the basement 's a bad idea .
They could just pour gas down the stairs and throw in a match .
We should stay in there and keep boarding up the windows . Shit , speaking of .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
Okay , we should each carry a weapon .
( GRUNTS )
( GROANING )
( SCREAMING )
So your dad bought this place to fix up ?
Yeah . Supposed to be his retirement project ,
something for him to work on , but I 'm pretty sure so far
he 's just paid other people to work on it .
Hey !
( BEDSPRINGS SQUEAK )
You 're gonna break this bed . It 's like a hundred years old .
Sorry . Your folks seem cool .
I mean , for people with money . You 're lucky .
( SCOFFS )
I guess . No , you are .
You don 't know what most people would give to have folks like yours .
( CRISPIAN SIGHS )
Whatever that means .
( CHUCKLES )
Come here .
So your brothers and sister get in tomorrow ?
Yeah . Tomorrow is my parents actual anniversary .
Thirty-five years , can you imagine ?
No . I can 't , really .
( BOTH CHUCKLING )
( GRUNTING )
( PANTING )
ERIN : Anyone know this guy ?
Although it 's kind of hard to tell .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
Hey . I 'm sure Crispian 's fine .
Crispian 's a tough guy .
No , he 's not , but thanks .
Thanks for the help , by the way .
Hey , you ... You seemed to have a handle on it .
Yeah , don 't worry about it .
( PANTING )
Hey , where 's your dad ?
Where 's the circuit box ?
I don 't know . I think it 's in the basement .
Why don 't you go look for it ? I 'm gonna go upstairs and try to find my dad .
Oh ! Dad !
Felix !
( WHISPERING ) One of them was in the bedroom .
They 've been watching us for days .
While we were sleeping .
This wasn 't a random attack , Felix . Dad , it 's okay .
Yeah . Calm down .
You understand what I 'm saying ? Our family is being targeted .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( GASPING )
( CHOKING )
( GURGLING )
Really ? You had to do that right in front of me ?
Are you saying something ?
Yeah , you know what ? Never mind .
You Okay ?
Yeah . I just ...
I just need to get washed up .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( WATER RUNNING )
( FAUCET HANDLE CREAKS )
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( FLOORBOARDS CREAKING )
( GRUNTING )
( YELLING )
( PLATES AND GLASSES SHATTERING )
( FOOTSTEPS )
( PANTING )
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( GASPS )
( YELLING )
( SCREAMS )
Hey .
Whoa . Whoa . Whoa .
( SCREAMING )
( GROANS )
( MAN SCREAMS THEN GROANING )
( LOCK CLICKS )
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
I woke up in there .
Yeah . You blacked out .
We put you there to hide you .
Thanks .
Welcome .
( GROANS )
Where 's Kelly ?
Uh ...
I don 't know .
( FOOTSTEPS )
Are you guys okay ? What 's going on ?
We heard noises , so we stayed upstairs .
What happened ?
One of them came in and attacked us .
I stabbed him and he ran away . Come on .
FELIX : You stabbed him ? ERIN : Yeah .
FELIX : Do you think you might have killed him ?
No , he ran out the door .
Was there anyone upstairs ?
We didn 't find anyone .
Whoever was there could have climbed out the window .
Is your dad okay ?
Yeah . He ... He just needed to lie down .
How many of them do you think there are ?
There 'd have to be at least two more of them .
Well , maybe they 're gone . Maybe you scared them off .
( GROANING )
Come here . Let 's not count on that . Come on .
There 's some tools left in the basement that I think we could use .
Let 's head down there .
Okay . Grab anything sharp or heavy that might make a good weapon
but you need to do it fast . We 've gotta be upstairs .
FELIX : Yeah , let 's go through Dad 's tools .
There 's plenty of stuff we could use there .
Zee , can you grab these ?
Okay . That 'll be enough to get started .
Let 's go . And don 't take too long !
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
ERIN : Drake doesn 't need to see her like this .
Zee , let me show you something quickly ?
( METAL CLATTERING )
Okay , so you just want to make sure
that the nail goes all the way through .
( HAMMERING )
See that ? Mm-hm .
Just do , say , four or five on this one ?
And we 'll just do as many as we can .
Okay .
Can I ask you something ?
( HAMMERING )
How did you learn all this stuff ?
Well , I had kind of a weird childhood .
I grew up on a survivalist compound .
I haven 't even told Crispian that yet .
Good answer .
Well , I guess when I was born , my dad got kind of paranoid .
He was convinced that the world
was gonna run out of resources in a matter of years .
Found a lot of guys who agreed with him , and we all moved to the Outback .
Basically , if things got too overpopulated , even out there ,
he wanted me to be able to take care of myself .
Moved to the States with Mom when I was 15
but I learned a lot beforehand .
Wow . That 's crazy .
Got some things here .
So nobody knows where Crispian is ?
No , he ... He ran out right after Kelly did .
All right . I gotta go look for them .
I at least have to try . I can 't leave Kelly out there .
What do you mean ? Drake , Kelly 's dead .
What ?
FELIX : Kelly 's dead . You didn 't know that ?
Oh , God . I 'm sorry .
I didn 't want to have to tell you like this , but she got killed .
Her body 's up there on the floor right now .
Drake , I 'm sorry . I- - Shut up ! Felix !
I know you cared about her . Shut up ! Shut up ! Stop talking !
( SLICING )
I 'm sorry .
( FLESH SQUELCHING )
( GRUNTS THEN GROANS )
( GRUNTING )
Would you just die already ?
This is hard enough for me .
Finished that one ? Mm-hm .
Cool . You know , it might not be a bad idea to do at least one more .
I 'm gonna go check on their dad upstairs .
When the boys come up , make sure they have some rope .
Uh , I can do it . I can go .
Do you wanna come with me ? We can go together .
No , that 's okay . I 'll just do another board .
Okay . Be careful .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( FLOORBOARD CREAKING )
( GRUNTING )
( GROANING )
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( GRUNTING )
( PANTING )
( FOOTSTEPS )
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( GRUNTING )
( GRUNTS )
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( YELLING )
MAN : Oh ! Oh , fuck !
Oh ! Oh , you motherfucker ! Oh , fuck !
FELIX : Hey . Would you mind checking on that ?
I believe this is what I 'm paying you for .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
Uh , thanks .
( SIGHS )
What a fucking disaster .
It 's okay , baby . It 'll be over soon .
( BOTH MOANING )
I 'm not really in the mood right now , Zee .
Come on . I 'll make it quick .
I want you to fuck me on this bed , next to your dead mom .
What ? Why would you even say something like that ?
( SIGHS )
You never want to do anything interesting .
I don 't think that 's a fair criticism .
Fuck me next to your dead morn , then .
This conversation is over .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
Hm .
MAN : Oh ! Fuck . Unh !
( GROANING )
Whoa , whoa , wait ! Don 't do that !
You don 't want your DNA in here , man .
I 'll clean it up later .
Just like the rest of this fucking mess .
Excuse me ? You say that like it 's my fault .
Listen . Just so we 're perfectly clear .
I just had to kill my own brother
because you guys keep getting beat up by some girl !
I had to stab my brother , more than once !
You were supposed to do that . For all the good you guys did in here ,
you could have stayed outside with your fucking crossbows !
You wanna talk about brothers ?
That 's my brother , laying dead right there .
And unlike you , I liked my brother .
Look , I 'm sorry . I didn 't know that .
I mean , I knew you guys served together .
I didn 't know you were related , though .
Man , she really fucked him up good , huh ?
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
I 'm just trying to think of reasons
why I shouldn 't kill you !
I 'll- - I 'll pay you more .
What 's that ?
You kill me , you get nothing .
You pull this off , I 'll give you 400,000 .
Okay ? I was supposed to give you 2 , right ?
But you should have your brother 's share . That 's only fair .
Plus , I 'll throw in an extra 100 . Each .
If we can finish this . Okay ? That 's half a million for you .
And 300,000 for you . I 'm looking at , uh ...
( FELIX GRUNTING )
I won 't- - I won 't be able to pay you until my inheritance comes through
but I 'll have it soon . We just need to finish this !
We did make it this far , man .
You two better be getting enough money to pay us !
Would I be doing this if I wasn 't ?
( CELL PHONE RINGING )
I got it .
( FOOTSTEPS )
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( GRUNTS THEN COUGHING )
Get up ! Get after her ! Get after her !
( GRUNTING )
( CLATTERING )
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
Hell , the cops could be driving here right now , for all we know .
What if they come across her down the road ? Did you even think about that ?
You need to calm down .
Don 't fucking tell me to calm down , Tom . This entire situation is out of control .
We don 't even know what 's going on .
She 's hurt . She 's not faster than us .
You stick to the road . You don 't see her , you come back here .
Well , where are you going ?
Back to the house to check on Craig
and to make sure she 's not doubling back .
Wait , give us the crossbow .
Look , you got your machete . We don 't have any weapons .
What are you standing there for ? Give it to me !
( LAUGHS )
You know how to use that thing ? I know how to fucking use it .
I pull the trigger , arrow shoots , right ?
Two bolts . Two shots .
You see her , you make it count .
Of course .
( GLASS CRUNCHING )
Shit .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( BULB SHATTERS )
( CLICKING )
( CLICKING CONTINUES )
( GROANING )
( ERIN GRUNTING )
( PANTING )
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
FELIX : What the fuck ?
I fucking hit her , didn 't I ? Get in there .
Give me the crossbow .
Come on !
All right . I 'm right behind you .
Okay .
Goddamn it .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( BOTH GRUNTING )
Fuck !
It 's not even hot , you dumb bitch . Whoa !
ELLS
( ZEE SHRIEKS )
( BOTH GRUNTING )
( GROANING )
( COUGHING )
( YELLING )
ELLS
( WHEEZES THEN COUGHS )
( BLENDER WHIRRING )
( SCREAMING )
( YELLING )
( COUGHING )
( ZEE PANTING )
( ZEE SCREAMS )
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( SHUDDERING )
( PANTING )
( CELL PHONE PLAYING RING-TONE )
( KEYPAD BEEPS )
MAN ( OVER PHONE ) : Felix ?
Hey . Felix , is it all done in there or what ?
I saw my signal came back . Is it over ?
Look , I know you 're pissed at me for not helping out .
I just- - I couldn 't do it , man . I- - I told you this might happen .
( CRISPIAN SIGHS OVER PHONE )
I saw Mom , and the blood , and you know I 'm a pacifist .
I can 't- - I can 't deal with the violent stuff .
Come on , now . I can hear you breathing on the other end of the phone .
Felix ?
It 's- - It 's fucking freezing out here . I 'm coming inside .
( FOOTSTEPS )
Erin .
You 're okay .
Where 's Felix ?
I stuck a blender in his head and killed him .
Oh .
Okay .
I can 't believe you were in on this .
( SIGHS )
Come on , babe . You do know how broke we are , right ?
You would have killed me .
No ! That was never supposed to happen .
Even if you hadn 't meant to kill me , you must have known I could have died .
No .
You were supposed to be the witness .
A person with a clean record
that could attest that our family and neighbors had been murdered
by unknown lunatics .
It was , in fact , a very important part of my plan that you be unharmed .
We needed someone with no motive to see what had happened here .
( SIGHS )
Someone other than Zee , obviously .
Where is Zee ?
I killed her too .
Oh .
Totally understand .
Listen . I 'm sorry things got so out of control ,
but how were we supposed to know
that you were really good at killing people ?
Which is actually sort of weird , by the way .
Had you reacted , um , normally ,
my parents and siblings would have been killed ,
you 'd have been untouched ...
and we 'd be rich .
We 'd be on our way to , like , a vacation in Paris .
Maybe an engagement ?
Okay . Okay .
( SNIFFLES )
There is a silver lining here , by the way .
I 'm now the sole inheritor of my family 's estate .
We 're talking millions , babe . You . Me .
Us .
Look .
Regardless of our current situation ...
or whatever we 're going through right now ...
it would be insane to throw that away .
I mean , look at all that would be wasted .
I understand it might take a while to make this up to you .
But in the meantime , let 's think about this logically .
I know you 've got your student loans .
How would $ 500,000 go towards fixing that problem ?
You could quit your bartending job , just study full time .
You know you hate that job .
You could have 500,000 within the month .
( SIGHS )
Or I go to jail ...
and you get nothing .
( SOFTLY ) Hey .
I love you .
I promised you that I 'd come back , didn 't I ?
Here I am .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
( COUGHING AND GASPING )
Why ?
Why the fuck not ?
( GUNSHOT )
( INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER )
Oh , fuck .
( GASPING )
We need medic and backup immediately at 5 Edelweiss Drive .
( ♪ ♪ ♪ )
No ! Don 't !
( GASPS )
( MIND THE GAP 'S " LOOKING FOR THE MAGIC " PLAYING )
♪ All my life I 've been Looking for the magic ♪
♪ I 've been looking for the magic ♪
♪ Fantasize on a sexy little tragic ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
♪ Oh , in her eyes To keep , oh , oh , oh ♪
♪ The magic in my eyes ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
♪ Baby , in my eyes ♪
♪ On the tips of Vegas Sexy little lay , girl ♪
♪ She been looking for the magic ♪
♪ Stay a while till the city is a desert ♪
♪ She 's been looking for the treasure ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
♪ Oh , in her eyes To keep , oh , oh , oh ♪
♪ The magic in my eyes ♪
♪ Baby , in my eyes ♪
♪ Because a photograph ls like an hourglass sometime ♪
♪ And then I never laugh Because I never have no time ♪
♪ Oh , in her eyes To keep , oh , oh , oh ♪
♪ The magic in my eyes ♪
♪ Baby , in my eyes ♪
♪ In my eyes ♪
♪ Oh , oh ♪
♪ In her eyes ♪
♪ Baby , in her eyes ♪
♪ Baby , in her eyes ♪ ♪